<resources>

    <string name="app_name">My Gym Application</string>

    // Select Goal Activity (Workout Program - 1st activity)
    <string name="select_target_activity_title">Choose your goal</string>
    <string name="checkbox_strength_header">Strength</string>
    <string name="checkbox_strength_description">Exercises to increase muscle strength</string>
    <string name="checkbox_mass_header">Mass</string>
    <string name="checkbox_mass_description">Exercises to increase muscle mass</string>
    <string name="checkbox_weight_loss_header">Weight loss</string>
    <string name="checkbox_weight_loss_description">Exercises that will help you lose weight</string>
    <string name="checkbox_stamina_header">Endurance</string>
    <string name="checkbox_stamina_description">exercises to increase your endurance</string>
    <string name="checkbox_line_header">Line</string>
    <string name="checkbox_line_description">Exercises for a perfect body line</string>
    <string name="checkbox_local_fat_header">Local fat</string>
    <string name="checkbox_local_fat_description">Remove local fat with these exercises</string>
    <string name="checkbox_flexibility_header">Flexibility</string>
    <string name="checkbox_flexibility_description">Exercises to improve your flexibility</string>
    <string name="select_target_btn_confirm_selections">Select</string>
    <string name="select_target_btn_reset_selections">Reset</string>


    // Select Muscle Activity (Workout Program - 2nd activity)
    <string name="select_muscle_activity_title">Select muscles to train</string>
    <string name="checkbox_biceps_header">Biceps</string>
    <string name="checkbox_biceps_description">Exercises for your biceps muscles</string>
    <string name="checkbox_chest_header">Chest</string>
    <string name="checkbox_chest_description">Improve your chest muscles</string>
    <string name="checkbox_triceps_header">Triceps</string>
    <string name="checkbox_triceps_description">Train your triceps</string>
    <string name="checkbox_back_header">Back</string>
    <string name="checkbox_back_description">Train all your back muscles</string>
    <string name="checkbox_shoulders_header">Shoulders</string>
    <string name="checkbox_shoulders_description">Shoulders and arm muscles</string>
    <string name="checkbox_abs_header">ABS</string>
    <string name="checkbox_abs_description">Abdominal muscles</string>
    <string name="checkbox_legs_header">Legs</string>
    <string name="checkbox_legs_description">Select to train all your legs muscles</string>
    <string name="checkbox_full_body_header">Full body</string>
    <string name="checkbox_full_body_description">Get exercises for all body</string>


    <string name="biceps_description_exercise_1">Concentration Curl Biceps Exercise — [Step-by-Step Technique] Step 1: Sit on the end of a bench, with a shoulder width foot stance. Brace your non-curling arm against your knee. Step 2: Hold the weight in your curling arm, with your arm fully stretched and your elbow touching against the inside of your knee. Step 3: Alternating arms, curl the weight up across your body, supinating your hand as you curl (pinky twisting out) and concentrating the squeeze in your biceps. Step 4: At the top of the movement, get a peak contraction by squeezing as hard as you can. Step 5: Keep your elbow against your knee throughout the movement, work at a 2 sec up, 3 sec down tempo. Step 6: Complete on each arm for the prescribed number of reps. ** Pro Tip: We recommend starting with 3 sets of 12-15 reps (each arm). **</string>
    <string name="biceps_description_exercise_2">TRX band exercises can be easily done from the comfort of your own home. This exercise is simple and can be added to your existing TRX arm workout. The TRX biceps curl can be done in 4 easy steps: Step 1: Ensure the TRX suspension is secured firmly at an elevated position. Grasp the handles with each hand, palms up and facing you. Step 2: Lean back with your feet together. Maintain a neutral position with your spine for the entire lift. Step 3: Using your biceps, bend your elbows and bring your body all the way to the handles. Step 4: LOWER YOURSELF BACK DOWN AND REPEAT.</string>
    <string name="chest_description_exercise_1">The dumbbell bench press is an awesome chest exercise that will help you build a great looking chest and overall physique. Doing the press with dumbbells is also much safer for your shoulders than using a barbell, because the dumbbell allows your arms to move in a more natural arc throughout the pressing motion. Doing the dumbbell bench press will also help build the stabilizer muscles in your shoulder that will make your shoulders functionally strong and will help you to avoid injury. Take a look at our dumbbell bench press form tutorial below where I guide you through the exercise and outline the main technique points of how to do a perfect dumbbell press. If you need something to print off and take to the gym as a reminder, the step-by-step exercise technique is further down this page. • Step 1: Sit on the end of a bench with the dumbbells resting on your thighs, holding them with a strong grip in the centre of the dumbbell grip. • Step 2: Lower yourself back and bring the dumbbells onto your chest, facing each other. • Step 3: Press the dumbbells up, so they are over your chest and your arms are almost straight. Twist your hands so your thumbs are side by side. • Step 4: Breathing in, slowly lower the dumbbells to a 2 count, so they reach a point in line with your nipples and your arms are just below 90 degrees. • Step 5: Breathing out and leading with your pinky finger, press the dumbbells back up to the start point, with your arms slightly bent. • Step 6: Repeat the dumbbell bench press for the prescribed number of reps. ** Pro Tip: We recommend starting 3 sets of 15-20 reps for the dumbbell bench press.**</string>
    <string name="chest_description_exercise_2">TRX Push-Ups — [Step-by-Step Technique] Step 1: Adjust the height of your suspension hoops to match the level of your knees. The higher the hoops, the easier the TRX push-up will be. Step 2: Take one hoop in each hand and make sure your shoulders are in line with your wrists. This will help to prevent shoulder injuries when completing the move. Move your legs behind you until your body is straight. This should be approximately a 45° angle to the floor. Step 3: Squeeze your abs and glutes to ensure your hips don’t sag. This is the starting position. Now slowly lower your body by bending your elbows. Do not get your body lower than your hands; you are likely to damage your shoulders. Step 4: Once you’ve completed the downward move you can lift your body back up by extending your arms. ** Pro Tip #1: To make it more difficult, squeeze your arms together at the elevated position. Push them back out before dropping down again. ** Pro Tip #2: Keep the action smooth or you’ll start spinning on the suspension cables and lose your balance. ** Pro Tip #3: It is essential to keep your spine straight while doing the TRX push-up. This will ensure you have proper form and are working the right muscles. ** Pro Tip #4: Focus on your core as you complete this exercise; you’ll feel the burn and the benefit.</string>
    <string name="chest_description_exercise_3">Use a stopwatch, a watch with a second hand or a phone app to track your time. Make sure you are completing full Push-Ups by dropping your elbows to a 90-degree angle at the bottom. Lock your arms out at the top and keep your abs and glutes tight throughout the movement.
\n•	Perform 10 Push-Ups
\n•	Rest 10 seconds
\n•	Perform nine Push-Ups
\n•	Rest nine seconds
\n•	Repeat this pattern all the way to the bottom of the pyramid (one Push-Up)\n
You will perform a total of 55 Push-Ups. The lactic acid will be burning throughout your upper body, much more so than what many athletes experience after an hour in the gym.
Continue performing this routine until you can start the pyramid at 20 Push-Ups and work your way down to one. The result will be a powerful upper body that translates onto the court, field or track for any sport.
</string>
    <string name="triceps_description_exercise_1">The dumbbell French press is an amazing exercise for increasing the size and strength in your triceps and is one of the only exercises to work all 3 heads of the triceps muscle. This exercise is also known as the lying French press or the skull crushers dumbbell exercise. All three of these exercises are a lying triceps press. Adding dumbbell skull crushers into your workout routine will help you to increase muscle mass and therefore the size of your arms. The main things to focus on when you do this exercise relate to the position of your upper arm. The first is to keep your elbows tight into your side, so they do not flare out. The second is to make sure your upper arm stays at 90 degrees to your body and doesn’t drop back over your head. This will take tension away from your triceps, resulting in a less effective squeeze. Lying Dumbell French Press — [Step-by-Step Technique] Step 1: Start by lying on a bench, holding a dumbbell in each hand, with them resting on your chest. Step 2: Press the dumbbells straight up in front of you and squeeze the handles. Step 3: Breathing in, slowly lower the dumbbells down, flexing at your elbow and keeping your elbows in tight. The dumbbells will stop just outside your ears. Step 4: Breathing out, press the dumbbells back up to the start position, flexing your triceps at the top and continuing to squeeze the dumbbells. ** Pro Tip #1: We recommend you start with 3 sets of 12-15 reps. ** Pro Tip #2: Using dumbbells instead of a barbell is healthier for your elbows, so for safety, we recommend this exercise as a start.</string>
    <string name="triceps_description_exercise_2">The TRX tricep extension is the best body weight triceps exercise for building muscle. This TRX triceps exercise is great to add to the end of your workout as your tricep workout finisher. Follow this video tutorial to start building your triceps today. TRX Tricep Extension — [Step-by-Step Technique] Step 1: Start with your back to the suspension trainer and take a handle over each shoulder with your grip on the main handle attachment. Step 2: Place your hands out in front of you so your arms are straight, then walk your feet back to a point where you feel the tension on your arms. Step 3: Breathing in and holding your neutral body position (head, shoulder, hips, knees, and ankles in line), slowly lower yourself forwards by bending your arms. The back of your hand should go towards your forehead. Step 4: Breathing out, press yourself back up into the start position, making sure to squeeze your triceps at the top of the movement. Step 5: Repeat steps 3 and 4 for the prescribed number of reps, then rest before completing your next set. ** Pro Tip #1: To start, complete this exercise with 2-3 sets of 10-15 reps. ** Pro Tip #2: Use this exercise within a functional training session, to make the most of the core stability work needed to control your body position.</string>
    <string name="back_description_exercise_1">** How To Do The Chest Supported Dumbbell Row Correctly - Proper Form, Sets and Reps Tutorial ** As you may know, there’s no shortage of rowing variations in the fitness world. You’ve got the barbell row, upright row, seated dumbbell row, bent-over row, and the list goes on. So, why should you care about yet another variation of this exercise, the chest supported dumbbell row? Well, the simple answer is that it’s one of the best exercises for really isolating your key back muscles. And as a result, it’s a great exercise to add on top of your back routine to see even better results. Some might think I’m a little crazy, but I like to think of the chest supported dumbbell row as the straightjacket variation. Why? Well, as you’ll see in the form demonstration, this exercise forces you to only use your back muscles to row the weights up, unlike other rowing variations where other muscle groups can come into play. And for that reason, the main focus here is on having the proper form and staying slow and controlled through the motion. The Chest Supported Dumbbell Row Setup (0:30) To do this exercise, you’re going to need a workout bench that you can adjust to an angle of around 45 degrees. It’s also beneficial to have the seat of the bench at a slight angle as well for added support. Now, one of the keys with this exercise is, before you begin to row the weights up, make sure to engage your back muscles by bringing your shoulder blades back and together. As you’ll see in the video, they shouldn’t move from this position. The Chest Supported Dumbbell Row Form Demonstration (1:15) With your feet firmly planted and shoulder blades back and engaged, start the rowing motion from your back, pretending your arms are cables bringing them up. This exercise is all about isolating your rhomboids, lats, and traps, so make sure that none of the lifting is coming from your arms, only your back. If you feel tension in your arms, you might try a lighter weight in order to dial in the proper form. Different Hand Positions and Variations (2:14) In addition to adjusting your weight to lock in the proper form of this exercise, you can also play around with different hand positions to see if one feels better for you. There really isn’t one right answer here, it’s all about finding the setup and technique that allows you to feel the proper tension in your back the most. Sets, Reps and Routine Recommendations For The Chest Supported Dumbbell Row (2:42) As promised I’m going to breakdown some of the recommendations I have for you on incorporating the chest supported dumbbell row into your training. Here’s the basic overview of what you’ll discover: - Not a primary back exercise, use a lighter weight at the end of your workout - 3 sets of around 8-15 reps. Higher reps are great for this exercise - Great to do at least 2 times per week, 3 sets each session</string>
    <string name="back_description_exercise_2">Strengthening your back muscles helps with posture, prevents injury, and eases the load on daily activities. Also called the inverted row, the TRX row is a body-weight back workout for strengthening the back, upper body, and core. The TRX version is an adaptation of traditional inverted rows but uses a suspension training system instead of a bar. If you don\'t have access to a suspension system, you can use a dip station or a secured barbell on a squat rack. Some gyms have gymnastic rings which work very well as an alternative to the row with TRX straps. TRX Back Row — [Step-by-Step Technique] Step 1: Anchor the suspension system and adjust the straps to hang just below the knee. Step 2: Grab both handles and make sure they are even. Step 3: Extend your arms and lean back keeping your spine neutral and walk forward. Step 4: Pull yourself up so that the handles touch your body. ** Pro Tip #1: Keep your body in a straight line throughout the entire exercise. ** Pro Tip #2: Squeeze the handles firmly throughout the entire lift. ** Pro Tip #3: Go lower to increase the resistance.</string>
    <string name="shoulders_description_exercise_1">** The Seated Arnold Press Exercise Guide - Discover The Proper Form and Routine Recommendations ** -Step 1: Sit on a bench, with either a slight decline from 90 degrees or completely vertical. -Step 2: Hold the dumbbells on your knees to start, then kick them up into a normal shoulder press position, with your arms at 90 degrees and the dumbbells level with your ears. -Step 3: Breathing out and squeezing the grip as tight as you can, press the dumbbells up overhead, bringing them slightly in front of your head. *Tip: You can touch the dumbbells together at the top of the movement, to make sure you get the squeeze into your shoulders. -Step 4: Breathing in, lower the dumbbells back down to the start point, then rotate them inwards in front of your face. *Note: At the lowest point, your upper arms should be parallel to the floor and your palms facing you. -Step 5: Breathing out, rotate your arms back out and press the weight upwards as in step 3. Repeat for the prescribed number of reps and sets. ** Pro Tip #1: We recommend you go slightly lighter in weight than with a normal shoulder press. ** Pro Tip #2: We recommend starting with 12-15 reps for 3 sets after you have done a bigger shoulder exercise.</string>
    <string name="shoulders_description_exercise_2">The Y fly exercise is great for strengthening your upper back, shoulders, and core. It\’s one of the best TRX shoulder exercises that you can add to the end of your workout. It combats getting a tight chest and rounded shoulders by strengthening your back muscles and creating the right balance between your chest and back muscles. You can find more TRX exercises for back, shoulder, and core strength by checking out the rest of our channel. TRX Y Fly Tutorial — [Step-by-Step Technique] Step 1: Start facing the suspension trainer and take a handle in each hand. Step 2: Place your feet forward, so you have a slight lean away from the suspension trainer, supporting your bodyweight. Slowly straighten your arms out in front of you. Step 3: Take a deep breath in, then as you breathe out, pull yourself forwards and upwards with your arms going above your head at about a 45-degree angle from your body, into a \'Y\' shape. Step 4: Breathing in, slowly lower yourself back to the start position, making sure to keep tension as you lower back. Step 5: Repeat steps 3 and 4 for the prescribed number of reps, then rest before completing your next set. ** Pro Tip #1: To start, complete this exercise as a finisher, with 2-3 sets of 12-15 reps. ** Pro Tip #2: Use this exercise within a functional training session, to make the most of the core stability work needed to control your body position.</string>
    <string name="abs_description_exercise_1">Lying leg raises are one of the best lower ab exercises for men at home. If you want to know how to do them correctly and make them 2 x more effective, you are in the right place. Most people do a leg raise lying down on the floor, which will work your abs if done correctly. In this tutorial, we show you how to do lying leg raises on a bench (or your bed) and make them 2 x more effective. When doing lying leg raises, correct form on a bench will pre-stretch your abs before you complete the raise part of the exercise. This causes better loading on the lower abs under tension and works them much harder. The most important part of this exercise is to make sure you keep your legs relatively straight throughout and rolling your pelvis under and up as you raise your legs. If you raise your legs by bending them, you will target your hip flexor muscle instead of your lower abs. Lying Leg Raise — [Step-by-Step Technique] Step 1: Start by lying on a bench (or your bed) with your hips just off the edge and your feet down so your tip-toes are on the floor. Breathe in. Step 2: As you breathe out, raise your legs up towards you, rolling your pelvis under and up to engage your lower abs. Step 3: As you reach the top point, your lower back should be slightly off the bench, and you should feel a squeeze in your abs. Step 4: Breathe in as you slowly lower your legs back down past the point of the bench so you get the stretch in your abs again (your toes do not need to touch the floor, and your lower back should not arch too much). ** Pro Tip #1: We recommend you start with 2 sets of 10-15 reps. ** Pro Tip #2: As you complete the exercise, think about rolling your pelvis on the raise and not over-arching your back on the lower.</string>
    <string name="abs_description_exercise_2">An ab fallout is a core exercise with a suspension. In this video, we use TRX for our fallout exercise. TRX ab exercises for building core strength are great because you can easily adjust the exercise to make it easier or harder. Step 1: Adjust the straps so the handles hang below the waist. Step 2: Grasp the handles and lean into the straps as if you were going to do a push-up. Step 3: Keeping your arms straight, lean into the suspension, and raise your arms up and over your head. Step 4: Maintain a neutral spine and keep the rest of your body straight, shoulders should be the only joints that move. Step 5: Pause momentarily during the peak of the exercise, then slowly return to the starting position.</string>
    <string name="legs_description_exercise_1">** The Goblet Squat Exercise Guide - The Proper Form, Sets and Routine Tutorial ** It\'s no secret that squats are a staple exercise for any leg training, muscle building routine. And, on top of that, squats can also be incredibly effective for fat loss. But what if you don\'t always want to go to the gym to get your squats in? Are there alternatives to traditional barbell back squats that you can do at home? Yes! As you\'ll discover in this goblet squat exercise guide, this variation of the traditional squat can be done with a single dumbbell or kettlebell and can be equally effective if done with the proper form, sets, and reps. So, in this goblet squat exercise guide, I\'m going to demonstrate the proper technique for the goblet squat, and I\'ll also give you some routine recommendations for both muscle building and fat loss. Here\'s the basic overview of the goblet squat exercise guide: - Step 1: Take a kettlebell or dumbbell and hold it in front of your chest. - Step 2: Set your feet just past shoulder width apart. - Step 3: Keeping your core tight and your torso upright, breath in as you lower down like you were sitting in a chair. - Step 4: At the low point of the move, your head and torso should be upright, your butt pushed back, legs at 90 degrees and heels firmly planted on the ground. - Step 5: Pause for 1 second at the bottom, then breathing out, push through your heels back to an upright position. ** Pro Tip #1: Start by using the higher rep range of 10-20 reps. ** Pro Tip #2: Try the different variations as I show in the video, to find the best one for you.</string>
    <string name="legs_description_exercise_2">The TRX single leg squat is one of the best TRX leg exercises to build explosive and powerful legs. Despite the difficulty involved, this is one of the safest leg workouts because you\'re only using your own body weight. Find out how to do a TRX squat properly and incorporate this exercise into your TRX leg workout.</string>
</resources>
